<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding AWS on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adding AWS on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/eks/</guid>
      <description>Set up EKS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECR</title>
      <link>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/ecr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/ecr/</guid>
      <description>To create an ECR repo for your images, navigate to the ECR dashboard in the AWS console.
In the ECR dashboard, click Create repository.
On the Create repository page, enter a name for the repository.
After naming the repository, scroll down to the section titled Image scan settings and click the toggle to enable Scan on push.
TIP: Configuring registry-level scan settings.
At the bottom of the page, click on the button to Create repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenID Connect</title>
      <link>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/oidc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/oidc/</guid>
      <description>TIP: What is OIDC? Why use it? Add a context to the job
what is a context? Set up OIDC In AWS, navigate to the IAM console.
In the navigation pane on the left side of the screen, click Identity providers.
In the next window, click Add provider.
To configure the provider, start by selecting the option for OpenID Connect.
The provider URL is in this format: https://oidc.circleci.com/org/ORGANIZATION_ID, where ORGANIZATION_ID refers to the organization you used to sign in to CircleCI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAM Roles and Permissions</title>
      <link>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/roles-permissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/chapters/3-adding-aws/roles-permissions/</guid>
      <description>Creating an IAM Role From the IAM dashboard, navigate to the Create role page by clicking Roles in the navigation pane then clicking the Create role button.
In the section titled Trusted entity type, select Web identity; and in the section titled Web identity, use the dropdown menu to select the IdP you created in the preceding section.
After selecting an IdP, use the Audience dropdown menu to select the audience you added in the preceding section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
